<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>  

    <RV2_EADD_SettingsTab>Esegn's Stuff</RV2_EADD_SettingsTab>

    <RV2_EADD_Settings_VorePathConflictsHeader>Vore Path Conflicts</RV2_EADD_Settings_VorePathConflictsHeader>

    <RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableVorePathConflicts>Enable vore path conflicts</RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableVorePathConflicts>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableVorePathConflicts_Tip>Prevents preds from engaging in two different vore paths that shouldn't work together. For example, they cannot endo-store one prey in their stomach and digest another at the same time. Forces a vore path switch to the first path if necessary to resolve a conflict.</RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableVorePathConflicts_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowConflictingManualInteractions>Allow conflicting manual interactions</RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowConflictingManualInteractions>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowConflictingManualInteractions_Tip>Manual vore interactions (i.e. initiated manually with right click) can be made despite path conflicts. This doesn't prevent the conflict, so the path will still switch when it gets a chance!</RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowConflictingManualInteractions_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowGoalSwitchersToProposeConflicting>Allow goal-switchers to propose conflicting paths</RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowGoalSwitchersToProposeConflicting>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowGoalSwitchersToProposeConflicting_Tip>Goal-switching predators (usually from the "Mischievous" quirk) can propose conflicting vore paths. These will switch to be non-conflicting. Applies to both manual and automatic vore.</RV2_EADD_Settings_AllowGoalSwitchersToProposeConflicting_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_PathConflictsIgnoreDesignations>Path conflicts ignore designations</RV2_EADD_Settings_PathConflictsIgnoreDesignations>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_PathConflictsIgnoreDesignations_Tip>If enabled, ignore designations for prey when resolving path conflicts. Overrides the above two settings in cases where it is necessary to prevent a conflict. Also stops goal-switching predators from making a path switch if it would cause a conflict that violates designations, unless the default option to make goal-switchers ignore designations is enabled.</RV2_EADD_Settings_PathConflictsIgnoreDesignations_Tip>

    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionHeader>Accidental Digestion</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionHeader>

    <RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableAccidentalDigestion>Enable accidental digestion</RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableAccidentalDigestion>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableAccidentalDigestion_Tip>Predators with endo prey who are sleeping, have reduced consciousness, or are under certain other conditions may randomly switch to a fatal goal, and their prey will have to get their attention to make them switch back.</RV2_EADD_Settings_EnableAccidentalDigestion_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_BaseAccidentalDigestionTickChance>Base accidental digestion chance</RV2_EADD_Settings_BaseAccidentalDigestionTickChance>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_BaseAccidentalDigestionTickChance_Tip>The base chance per rare game tick (there are 10 per in-game hour) that a predator will start accidentally digesting endo prey. The chance is rolled independently per-prey (or per "part" if path conflicts are enabled), and is only rolled if a predator is in an applicable state/situation (for example, sleeping). The chance may be modified based on the predator's state and quirks.</RV2_EADD_Settings_BaseAccidentalDigestionTickChance_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionChanceExample>Total chance over {0} ticks: {1}%</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionChanceExample>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionChanceExample_Tip>If accidental digestion was rolled for at the base chance for this many ticks in a row, this is the percent chance it would happen. For reference, the default temporary hold oral vore path has prey in the stomach for 36 ticks. Bear in mind accidental digestion may not be always possible to start over the whole duration.</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionChanceExample_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionIgnoresDesignations>Accidental digestion ignores designations</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionIgnoresDesignations>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionIgnoresDesignations_Tip>If enabled, accidental digestion can happen to prey even if they are designated with fatal disabled.</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionIgnoresDesignations_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionNotificationType>Accidental digestion notification type</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionNotificationType>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionNotificationType_Tip>What kind of notification, if any, you want to see when accidental digestion happens. Set it to "None" if you'd like it to be as much a surprise for you as it is for the predator!</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionNotificationType_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_BasePredatorAwarenessChance>Base predator awareness chance</RV2_EADD_Settings_BasePredatorAwarenessChance>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_BasePredatorAwarenessChance_Tip>Base chance per tick that a predator becomes aware they've started accidentally digesting their prey. Modified by quirks and how effectively the prey struggles, if relevant.</RV2_EADD_Settings_BasePredatorAwarenessChance_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_PredatorAwarenessChanceExample>Total over warmup phase: {0}%</RV2_EADD_Settings_PredatorAwarenessChanceExample>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_PredatorAwarenessChanceExample_Tip>The "warmup" phase of fatal digestion lasts for 24 ticks. This is the total chance a predator at the base awareness chance per tick will notice that they are accidentally digesting over that many ticks.</RV2_EADD_Settings_PredatorAwarenessChanceExample_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_PreyMustStruggleToBeNoticed>Prey must struggle to be noticed</RV2_EADD_Settings_PreyMustStruggleToBeNoticed>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_PreyMustStruggleToBeNoticed_Tip>If enabled, a predator can only notice they are accidentally digesting their prey if the prey is struggling. Ignored if struggling is disabled as a mechanic. If prey is unable to struggle, the predator will never notice that they are accidentally digesting them!</RV2_EADD_Settings_PreyMustStruggleToBeNoticed_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_CanAlwaysAccidentallyDigest>Accidental digestion always possible</RV2_EADD_Settings_CanAlwaysAccidentallyDigest>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_CanAlwaysAccidentallyDigest_Tip>Ordinarily, accidental digestion can only start if a predator is sleeping or has reduced consciousness. If this setting is enabled, it can happen at any time.</RV2_EADD_Settings_CanAlwaysAccidentallyDigest_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_LongTermPreventsAccidentalDigestion>Long-term stages prevent accidental digestion</RV2_EADD_Settings_LongTermPreventsAccidentalDigestion>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_LongTermPreventsAccidentalDigestion_Tip>If enabled, accidental digestion cannot begin if it would affect prey that have a manual pass condition stage, i.e. the long-term store goal. Keeps belly pets and the like safe.</RV2_EADD_Settings_LongTermPreventsAccidentalDigestion_Tip>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionCooldown>Accidental digestion cooldown</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionCooldown>
    <RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionCooldown_Tip>For any given predator, wait this many ticks after accidental digestion starts before it can happen again. For reference, 60000 ticks is one in-game day.</RV2_EADD_Settings_AccidentalDigestionCooldown_Tip>

</LanguageData>